[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word is defined as \u201cthe spiritual attitude of a man to a god and a dog to a man\u201d in Ambrose Bierces satirical book The Devils Dictionary?", "correct_answer": "Reverence", "incorrect_answers": ["Love", "Worship", "Respect"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which musical act performed at the charity event at the end of the movie Rat Race?", "correct_answer": "Smashmouth", "incorrect_answers": ["Hot Chocolate", "Better Than Ezra", "The Four Tops"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A human in which film delivered this ruthless line?\nI say we take off and nuke the entire site from orbit. Its the only way to be sure.", "correct_answer": "Aliens", "incorrect_answers": ["Starship Troopers", "Alien3", "When Worlds Collide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Dibbuk Box, which presumably contained a spirit, was what type of box?", "correct_answer": "Wine Cabinet Box", "incorrect_answers": ["Jewelery Box", "Christmas Gift Box", "Shoe Box"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What American president was known for having an orchard garden with peach trees at his Moticello estate?", "correct_answer": "Thomas Jefferson", "incorrect_answers": ["George Washington", "Abraham Lincoln", "John Adams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Rocky Horror Picture Show  (1975) is not one of the Top 100 AFI films.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mercury has a moon called Celsius.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1995, Drew Barrymore shocked everyone when she did this at the Late Show with David Letterman.", "correct_answer": "Showed David Letterman her breasts", "incorrect_answers": ["Grabbed Daves behind and gave him a French kiss", "Took off her underwear and gave it to Dave as a present", "Took her dress off and remained only in her underwear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor plays Craigs dad in the 1995 movie Friday?", "correct_answer": "John Witherspoon", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim Brown", "Bernie Mac", "Laurence Fishburne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how many reindeer live in Eurasia?", "correct_answer": "5 million", "incorrect_answers": ["10 million", "15 million", "1 million"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What physical reaction is pepper believed to stimulate?", "correct_answer": "Sneezing", "incorrect_answers": ["Vomiting", "Coughing", "Crying"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It would be better to skip breakfast entirely than to eat the typical American breakfast of sausage, sweets rolls, pancakes with syrup, and eggs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]